Democratic Study Group Records
Manuscript Division, Library of Congress
- Part II: Services and Activities, 1937-1994 (Box II:87-102)
  - Campaign file (Box II:87)
    - Congressional campaigns
      - 1964
        - Chronological file, 1963-1964, (3 folders)
        - Material sent to candidates
        - Printed matter
        - Seminar
          - Miscellany
          - Transcript, (1 folder) (Box II:89)
      - 1966
        - Chronological file, 1965-1967, undated, (4 folders)
        - Funding, 1966
        - Printed matter, 1966
        - Questionnaire, 1966
      - 1968
        - “Campaign cards,” 1968
        - Chronological file, 1966-1969, (2 folders) (Box II:90)
        - Fund raising, 1968
        - Funding, 1968
        - Manual, 1968
        - Marginal districts, 1967-1968
        - News clippings, 1967-1968
        - Notes and candidate lists, 1968
        - Questionnaires, 1967-1968
        - Roll call vote supplements, 1967-1968 (Box II:91)
      - 1970
        - Campaign seminars for non-incumbent candidates
          - First, 1969-1971, (2 folders)
          - Second, 1970, (2 folders)
        - Chronological file, 1969-1970
        - Contributions, 1970
        - Funding, 1970
      - 1972
        - Candidate information
        - Chronological file, (1 folder) (Box II:92)
        - Election night tally sheets
        - Fund-raising letter
        - Funding
        - Key Democratic primaries
        - Key House of Representatives election contests
          - Distribution copies
          - Originals
        - McGovern, George
      - 1974, chronological file
      - 1976
        - Chronological file, 1975-1976
        - Funding, 1976
        - Vote records, 1976
      - 1978
        - Chronological file, 1977-1978
        - Printed matter, 1978 (Box II:93)
      - 1980
        - Chronological file, 1980-1981
        - Political action committees, 1980
        - Printed matter, 1979-1980
      - 1982
        - Campaign financing, 1981
        - Chronological file, 1982
        - Election survey, 1982
        - Printed matter, 1982
      - 1984 (Box II:94)
        - Chronological file, 1984-1985
        - Citizens Against PACs See Container II:116, same heading
        - Indiana (8th district), 1984-1985, (3 folders)
      - 1988, chronological file
      - Unidentified campaigns, undated
    - Contested elections
      - Chronological file, 1937, 1950, 1960-1967, undated, (3 folders)
      - Peterson, Stephen M., 1964-1965
    - Election results, 1968-1981 (Box II:95)
    - Electors, 1960-1964
    - Labor union membership votes, 1962-1968
    - Miscellany, 1956, 1966, 1976, 1988, undated
    - Phone polling guide, 1984
    - Presidential elections
      - 1960, chronological file
      - 1964
        - Chronological file, 1964-1965
        - News clippings, 1963-1964
        - Wallace, George C.
      - 1968
        - Chronological file
          - 1965-1966, (1 folder)
          - 1967-1969, (1 folder) (Box II:96)
        - Political cartoons, 1967-1968, (3 folders)
      - 1980
        - Anderson, John B.
        - Chronological file
        - Democratic Party convention
      - 1984
        - Chronological file, 1981-1984
        - Hart, Gary
    - Vote analysis, special elections, 1974
  - Executive agency contact lists
    - 1975-1980
    - 1992
  - New member services
    - Freshmen orientations
      - 1966
      - 1970
      - 1972 (Box II:97)
      - 1974
        - Miscellany
        - Roster and phone numbers
      - 1976
        - Brochure
        - Correspondence
        - Manual
        - Miscellany
      - 1978
        - Brochure, 1978
        - Correspondence, 1978-1979
        - “The First Weeks: From Victory through Confusion to Effectiveness,” 1978 (Box II:98)
        - Manual, (3 folders)
        - Miscellany
        - Reception
      - 1980
        - Correspondence, 1980-1981
        - Manual, 1980
        - Miscellany, 1980 (Box II:99)
      - 1982
        - Information packet, 1982
        - Manual, 1982
        - Miscellany, 1982
        - Program, 1982
        - Reception, 1982-1983
        - Reimbursements, 1982-1983
      - 1984
        - Manual, 1983-1984
        - Miscellany, 1983-1985
        - Program, 1984 (Box II:100)
        - Reception, 1984-1985
      - 1986
        - Manual, (2 folders)
        - Program
        - Reception
      - 1988
        - Manual
        - Miscellany
      - 1990
      - 1994, (2 folders) (Box II:101)
      - Miscellany, 1970-1977, 1986-1989, undated
  - Seminars and briefings on legislative issues, 1969-1971, 1977
  - Whip system
    - Calls, 1969-1977, (2 folders)
    - General file, 1961-1969, 1976, 1985-1987, (3 folders)
    - Lists, 1965-1975
    - Notices, 1968-1969
    - Study, impact of whip system on votes, 1967-1969, (1 folder); (4 folders) (Box II:102)
  - Workshops on office organization and management, 1975-1977
- Part II: Subject File, 1912-1995 (Box II:102-185)
  Correspondence and memoranda, briefing books, position papers, resolutions and rule making, legal documents, government records, voting and hearing records, committee and caucus records, research materials, draft legislation, surveys, press releases and media files, news clippings and printed matter.
  - Agnew, Spiro T., 1973, undated (Box II:102)
  - Anti-ballistic missile system, 1969
  - Appropriations
    - Amendments, 1971-1974
    - General file, 1948-1951, 1961-1967, 1980-1983
    - Riders, 1977
    - Aspin, Les
    - Leath, Marvin
    - Notes
    - Vote records of candidates (Box II:103)
  - Arms control, 1983-1987
  - Bolling Committee See Container II:131, Select Committee on Committees, 1974
  - Boundary Waters Canoe Area, 1975-1978, undated, (5 folders)
  - Budget
    - Chronological file
      - 1963, 1973-1974, (1 folder)
      - 1979-1990, (6 folders) (Box II:104)
      - 1991-1993, undated, (3 folders) (Box II:105)
    - House budget
      - Chronological file, 1973-1986, (2 folders)
      - Committee funding charts, 1981
      - Legislation, 1973-1974, (2 folders)
  - Campaign finance reform
    - Chronological file
      - 1966-1976
      - 1977, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:106)
      - 1978-1982, (3 folders)
      - 1983, (2 folders) (Box II:107)
      - 1984-1986, (6 folders)
      - 1987, (8 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:108, Box II:109)
      - 1988, undated, (1 folder)
    - Correspondence, 1979-1986
    - Dear colleague letters, 1977-1979
    - Federal Election Commission, printed matter, 1977-1983
    - Full tax credit
      - Chronological file, 1985-1986, (2 folders)
      - Roll Call article, 1986
    - H.R. 1
      - Amendments, 1979
      - Certification procedure, 1979
      - Chronological file, 1979
        - Jan.-June, (2 folders)
        - July-Dec., (2 folders) (Box II:110)
      - Congressional Record, 1979
      - Correspondence
        - House Administration Committee, 1979
        - Member responses to constituent mail, 1979
        - Opposition, 1979, (2 folders)
      - Cost of public financing, 1979
      - Federal Election Commission (Box II:111)
        - Correspondence, 1979
        - Financial reports, 1977-1978, (2 folders)
      - Financial research
        - Ceiling study, 1979
        - Chronological file, 1979, (3 folders)
        - Political action committees, 1979
        - Total spending, 1979
      - Former members of Congress, letter to editor, 1979 (Box II:112)
      - Hearings, 1979, (2 folders)
      - Lists, 1979
      - Miscellany, 1979
      - Press and public reactions, 1979
      - Printed matter, 1979
      - Public financing, 1978-1979 (Box II:113)
      - Radio-spots, 1979
      - Rebuttal arguments, 1979
      - Sponsors, 1979
      - Tax check-off, 1977-1979
      - Whip check list, 1979
    - H.R. 4970, 1979 (Obey-Railsback bill)
      - Amendments
      - Arguments against
      - Briefing book
      - Drafts
      - Miscellany
      - Obey, David R., information for DSG members
      - Questions and answers (Box II:114)
      - Statements
      - Whip file
    - H.R. 7277, 1982
    - H.R. 11315
      - Amendment, 1978
      - Chronological file, 1978, (3 folders)
      - Foley, Thomas S., statements, 1978
      - House Administration Committee
        - Campaign finance analysis, briefing books, 1978, (2 folders)
        - Hearings (Box II:115)
          - 1982 June 10
          - 1983 Jan. 26-27
          - 1983 June 16
          - 1987 June 30
        - Member requests to report on legislation, 1977
      - Spending analysis, 1978
      - Whip file, 1978
    - McHugh-Tauke amendment (H.R. 3780), 1985
    - Miscellaneous bills, 1973, 1981-1982
    - News clippings, 1978-1985 (Box II:116)
    - Political action committees (PACs)
      - Chronological file, 1978-1986, (4 folders)
      - Citizens Against PACs, 1984, (2 folders)
      - Committee assignments and PAC contributions, study, 1979
      - Conferences and meetings
        - American Bar Association, “The Role of Political Action Parties in Campaign Financing,” Charlottesville, Va., 1986
        - “Parties, Interest Groups, and Campaign Finance Laws,” Washington, D.C., 1979, (1 folder); (2 folders) (Box II:117)
        - Political Science Association annual meeting, Washington, D.C., 1984
        - Public Affairs Council, PAC Conference, Washington, D.C., 1986
      - Election comparisons
        - 1976-1978, 1978
        - 1978-1980, 1980
        - 1978-1982, 1982
      - Financial records, 1977-1982, (2 folders)
      - Letters to editor, 1979
      - Miscellany, 1979
      - Printed matter, 1978-1987, (2 folders) (Box II:118)
      - Statistics, 1976-1979
    - Public financing, 1967, 1974-1984, (3 folders)
    - Senate hearings, 1986
    - Spending ceilings, 1976
    - Survey, 1987
    - Tax credits
      - Chronological file
        - 1972-1983, (2 folders)
        - 1986-1987, (1 folder) (Box II:119)
      - Miscellany, 1982-1983
      - Political Tax Credit Act of 1983, 1982-1985, (4 folders)
      - Revenue loss, 1979-1984
      - Small Contribution Tax Credit Reform Act, 1985-1986, undated
        - 1985, (2 folders)
        - 1986, undated, (2 folders) (Box II:120)
  - Caucus groups, 1977-1980, (2 folders)
  - Carter, Jimmy, presidential administration See Container II:184, White House staff, survey of performance, 1979
  - Censure, 1965-1967, undated
  - Coalition of southern Democrats and conservative Republicans, 1950-1965, (3 folders)
  - Committee on Standards of Official Conduct, 1985 (Box II:121)
  - Committee records retention, 1990
  - Congress
    - American Enterprise Institute, studies, 1965
    - Behavior, 1952-1953, 1959-1963, 1979
    - Canadian trip, members and former members of Congress, 1983-1985
    - Capitol page residence, 1963
    - “Congressional Attitudes toward Congressional Operations and Procedures,” 1977
    - Effectiveness, 1955-1964
    - “A House Divided,” television broadcast, transcript, 1978
    - House of Representatives
      - Bank
        - 1954, 1986-1991
        - 1992, (2 folders) (Box II:122)
      - Committees, 1973-1986, undated
      - Family and Medical Leave Act, 1993
      - Functions, Congressional Research Service report, 1976
      - Majority leader election, 1969-1971
      - Members
        - Chronological file, 1959-1986, undated, (3 folders)
        - Dymally, Mervyn M., 1981
        - McHugh, Matthew Francis, 1982-1983
        - Richmond, Frederick W., 1982 (Box II:123)
      - Miscellany, 1970, 1981-1983, undated
      - Task forces, 1976-1977
      - Ways and Means Committee, chairmanship election, 1971
      - Whip election, 1986
    - News clippings, 1955-1963
    - Organization
      - 94th Congress, 1974-1975, (2 folders)
      - 95th Congress, 1977
    - Pensions, 1968
    - Salaries
      - Chronological file, 1962-1963, 1975-1989, (4 folders)
      - Notes, 1977 (Box II:124)
      - Task force on member's compensation, 1981-1983
    - Senate, printed matter, 1959-1963
    - Staff costs, 1979-1981
    - Tax deductions, 1982
  - Congressional reform See also Containers II:136-141, Reform
    - Amendments and proposals, 1982, undated
    - American Political Science Association, study, 1961-1964, (3 folders)
    - Blakeslee, Lucinda B., 1978
    - Chronological file
      - 1913, 1951, 1958-1965, (3 folders)
      - 1966-1979, (9 folders) (Box II:125)
      - 1981-1986, (6 folders) (Box II:126)
      - 1991-1994, undated
    - Commission on Administrative Review (Obey Commission), 1977, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:127)
    - Committee on Organization, Study, and Review (Hansen Committee), 1970-1971
    - Dryfoos Conference on Public Affairs, Dartmouth College, Hanover, N.H., 1964
    - Heymann, Philip B., case study, 1975
    - Joint Committee on the Organization of Congress
      - Chronological file
        - 1946, 1963
        - 1965-1966, (2 folders) (Box II:128)
      - Hearings, printed matter, 1965
    - Legislative Reorganization Act of 1970, 1970
      - Amendments, (2 folders)
      - Correspondence
      - Democratic Study Group reports
      - Legislation
      - Miscellany (Box II:129)
      - News clippings
      - Printed matter, 1967-1970, (2 folders)
      - Whip material
    - News clippings
      - General, 1954-1975, undated, (3 folders)
      - Scrapbook, 1957-1969
    - Printed matter
      - 1927, 1950-1969
      - 1970-1975, undated, (2 folders) (Box II:130)
    - Questionnaire, 1970, (2 folders); (1 folder) (Box II:131)
    - Record teller votes
      - Division voting, 1969-1970
      - General file, 1970-1978, (2 folders)
    - Select Committee on Committees (Bolling Committee), 1974
    - Survey research See Containers II:164-165, same heading
  - Correspondence
    - General
      - 1964-1967, 1978-1979, (2 folders)
      - 1980
        - Jan.-June, (2 folders)
        - July-Dec. (Box II:132)
      - 1981-1990, (4 folders)
      - 1993
    - Special
      - 1959-1966, (3 folders)
      - 1967-1984, (10 folders) (Box II:133)
      - 1985-1990, (3 folders) (Box II:134)
      - 1991-1994, undated, (2 folders)
  - Defense, 1964-1970, 1977-1990
  - Democratic Caucus
    - Amendments and rule changes, 1970-1974, undated, (2 folders)
    - Chronological file
      - 1921, 1960-1963, 1972-1974, (2 folders)
      - 1975-1988, (9 folders) (Box II:135)
    - Committee assignments, 1958-1964, (2 folders)
    - Fiscal 1987 budget outlays, 1986 (Box II:136)
    - Indicted committee chairmen, 1971-1980, undated
    - Meeting transcripts, 1971-1983, (2 folders)
    - Membership, 1976
    - Organization, 1983-1984
    - Reform See also Containers II:124-131, Congressional reform
      - Amendments, 1977-1987, undated
      - Budget Committee, 1973-1975
      - Caucus binding, 1912-1921, 1934, 1949, 1974-1975, undated
      - Chronological file
        - 1960-1970, (2 folders)
        - 1971-1974, Nov., (8 folders) (Box II:137)
        - 1974, Dec.-1978, (9 folders) (Box II:138)
        - 1979-1985, (3 folders) (Box II:139)
        - 1992-1993, undated, (3 folders)
      - Committee on Organization, Study and Review (Frost Committee), 1984-1988, undated, (4 folders)
      - Floor amendments, 1977 (Box II:140)
      - News clippings, 1974-1976
      - Notes, 1980
      - Rules
        - Proposed changes, 1976, 1982-1985, undated, (4 folders)
        - Recodification, 1976-1977, undated
        - Resolutions, undated
      - Speaker's power, 1981-1984, undated
      - Whip position, proposal to elect, 1985 (Box II:141)
    - “Responsible party model,” by Richard A. Conlon See Container II:2, same heading
    - Steering and Policy Committee, 1965-1982, (2 folders)
    - Votes, 1969-1972
    - Waiver of Rule 31, 1987
  - Democratic Issues Conference, White Sulfur Springs, W.Va., 1986
  - Democratic Forum, Montgomery County, Md., 1961-1965
  - Democratic National Committee
    - Chronological file
      - 1967-1972, 1981-1986
      - 1991
    - Conference, Philadelphia, Pa., 1982
  - Democratic Party
    - Discipline
      - Chronological file, 1960-1970, 1980-1982, undated
      - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party See Container II:152 (Box II:142)
      - Rarick, John R., 1967-1969
      - Rivers, L. Mendel, 1964-1969
      - Watson, Albert W., and John Bell Williams, 1964-1967
    - “Domestic accomplishments,” 1977
    - History, printed matter, 1932, 1962-1967
    - Platform, 1972, 1984, (3 folders)
  - District of Columbia
    - Chronological file, 1963-1973, 1991
    - McMillan, John L., chairmanship challenge, 1970-1971
  - Doonesbury, 1979
  - Economy
    - 1959, 1969-1988
    - 1991-1993
  - Education
    - Chronological file,1956-1960, 1979, 1989-1990
    - Elementary and Secondary Education Act, amendments, 1967 (Box II:143)
  - El Salvador, aid program, 1981, 1990
  - Election law
    - Contested elections See Container II:94, same heading
    - Presidential election, House of Representatives role, 1968, 1976-1980, (2 folders)
    - Reform, 1963-1967, 1975, 1982-1983, (2 folders)
  - Energy, oil, 1974-1979
  - Federal Communications Commission, 1964-1969
  - Finance
    - Garn, Jake, 1985-1986
    - Pratt, Richard T.
      - Quotes, 1980-1982
      - “Speeches, testimony, and interviews,” 1981-1982, (3 folders); (2 folders) (Box II:144, Box II:145)
    - Savings and loan issue
      - 1977-1987, (5 folders)
      - 1988-1990, (7 folders) (Box II:146)
      - 1990, (2 folders) (Box II:147)
      - 1991
  - Ford, Gerald R., 1966
  - Foreign Affairs Steering Committee, 1963-1966
  - Foreign aid, 1978-1979
  - Foreign policy, 1980, 1986-1992
  - Franking privilege in Congress, 1979-1985, undated
  - Fraser, Donald MacKay, Minnesota senate campaign, 1977-1978, undated
    - California
    - Chronological file, (3 folders)
    - Fund-raiser, 1978 July 20 (Box II:148)
    - Lists
      - Contributors
      - Volunteers
    - News clippings
    - Notes
    - Public relations, 1974-1978
    - Scheduling file, 1978
    - Summary of contributions
    - “Survey of the Political Climate in Minnesota”
    - Trade record, 1973-1978
  - Frost Committee See Container II:139, Committee on Organization, Study and Review
  - Full Employment Steering Committee, 1965-1966
    - Correspondence
    - Miscellany
    - Press releases
    - Printed matter, 1963-1967
    - Reports
  - Galbraith, James K., 1974 (Box II:149)
  - Gans, Curtis, political advertising proposal, 1983-1984
  - Gilder, George, debate with Robert B. Reich, 1986-1987
  - Grain sales to Soviet Union, 1986
  - Gramm-Rudman budget deficit reduction measures
    - Chronological file, 1981-1988, (3 folders)
    - Press coverage, 1985
  - Hansen Committee See Container II:127, Committee on Organization, Study, and Review
  - Hays, Wayne L., 1972-1975
  - Health care, 1991-1992, (2 folders)
  - Heritage Foundation, 1980
  - Housing, 1965-1967, 1986-1988, (2 folders)
  - Informal groups in Congress, 1979-1980, undated
  - Iran, ban on travel to, Ramsey Clark, 1978-1980 (Box II:150)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., presidential administration
    - Great Society, 1965-1967
    - Southwick, Paul, 1964
      - “Administration record”
      - “Nineteen Sixty Four: A Year of Progress”
  - Justice Department, reorganization, 1949-1953, 1967-1968
  - Lebanon, 1983
  - Legislation (Box II:151)
    - Chronological file
      - 1948-1989, (4 folders)
      - 1991-1993, undated
    - Democratic Study Group positions, 1960-1984, undated, (2 folders)
  - Lobbyists, lists, 1965-1968, undated
  - Meat import quotas, 1964
  - Military conscription proposals, 1980
  - Miscellany (Box II:152)
    - Correspondence and related material, 1964-1967, 1976, undated
    - Printed matter
      - 1947-1953, 1960-1985, (3 folders)
      - 1986-1995, undated
  - Mississippi Freedom Democratic Party
    - Challenge papers, 1964-1965, (2 folders)
    - Chronological file, 1960-1971, (3 folders)
    - Mondale, Walter, Senate campaign schedule, 1966 (Box II:153)
  - News clippings, 1962-1985, (4 folders)
  - Nicaragua and contra aid, 1986-1988, (2 folders)
  - Nixon, Richard M., presidential administration
    - Impeachment, 1973-1974
    - Income and taxes, 1973
    - Popularity, 1972
    - Watergate scandal, news clippings See Containers II:178-184, same heading
  - Obey Commission See Containers II:126-127, Commission on Administrative Review
  - Office of Equal Opportunity, printed matter, 1968
  - O'Neill, Thomas P., Symposium on the United States Congress, Boston College, Boston, Mass., 1981 Jan. 29-31
    - Correspondence and notes, 1981-1982
    - Remarks, 1981, (1 folder) (Box II:154)
  - Organizations
    - AFL-CIO, 1967, 1977-1980, undated
    - American Foundation for Continuing Education, 1959-1963, undated
    - American Political Foundation, 1977-1983
    - American Political Science Foundation, Law and Political Process Study Group, 1986
    - America's Unifying Movement, 1966
    - Board of Christian Social Concerns of the United Methodist Church, 1972
    - Congressional Black Caucus, 1982-1983
    - Democrats for the 80's, 1982
    - Miscellaneous, 1960-1981, 1991, undated
    - National Association of Realtors
      - Congressional voting
        - 1980, (2 folders)
        - 1982, (1 folder) (Box II:155)
      - Miscellany, 1976-1980, 1986
    - National Committee for an Effective Congress, 1964-1968, 1978
    - National Endowment for Democracy
      - Chronological file
        - 1983, (5 folders)
        - 1984-1987, undated, (6 folders) (Box II:156)
      - Phone records and fund-raising, 1984-1987, (2 folders)
    - National Federation of Independent Business, 1981-1982 (Box II:157)
    - National Taxpayer's Union
      - Chronological file, 1980-1986, (2 folders)
      - Miscellany, 1979-1984, (3 folders)
    - New England Regional Commission, 1977-1978
    - Project Vote, 1986-1987
    - Roosevelt Center for International Policy Studies, Washington, D.C., 1982
  - Persian Gulf, 1987-1988, (2 folders)
  - Policy initiatives, 99th Congress, 1985-1986
  - Polls, 1985-1986 (Box II:158)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton (1908-1972)
    - Chronological file, 1964-1966, undated
    - News clippings, 1963-1967
  - Ralph Nader Congress Report, 1972
  - Reagan, Ronald, presidential administration
    - Budget speech, responses, 1982
    - Ethics inquiries, 1987
    - Redistricting, 1958, 1967
  - Reform See Containers II:124-131, Congressional reform; Containers II:136-141, same heading; and Containers II:161-162, Proposed changes
  - Republican Party
    - Chronological file, 1956-1967, 1973-1976, 1986-1988, (4 folders)
    - Popularity Report, 1974
    - Research groups, member contributions, 1979
    - Survey, 1977
  - Right-wing groups, contributions to, 1965-1967
  - “Rubber stamp” issue, 1965
  - Rules (Box II:159)
    - Committee, 1958-1966, 1973, (3 folders)
    - Project Saltmine, index-digest of House precedents
      - Procedures and justification for, 1963-1966
      - Research file
        - Adjournment, 1944, 1951, 1961, undated
        - Amendments, 1932-1940, 1949, 1963, undated
        - Appropriation on legislative bill, 1935-1938, 1961
        - Clearly covered, 1933, 1940-1949
        - Codified, 1966
        - Conferees powers and jurisdiction, 1932-1966, (2 folders)
        - Congressional Record and Journal, 1934-1938, 1945-1950, 1959, 1965
        - Consideration, 1932-1966
        - Contempt citations, 1946-1956, 1966
        - Discharge rule and 21-day rule, 1932-1966
        - Division of resolution, 1932-1934
        - Germaneness, 1932-1965, (2 folders) (Box II:160)
        - Jurisdiction of committees, 1953, 1963-1964
        - Legislation on appropriations bill, 1932-1965, (3 folders)
        - Member's conduct, 1944-1946, 1952-1955
        - Miscellaneous, 1933-1935, 1954, 1961-1965
        - Motion to table, 1962-1965, undated
        - Omnibus claims bill, 1935-1937
        - Personal privilege, 1932-1962, (2 folders)
        - Precedents of the House of Representatives, 1954-1969, undated